curriculumpathways.com 2011-03-14

# SAS® Curriculum Pathways® Privacy Statment

**Our Commitment to Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect that privacy, we are providing this notice to explain our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

**The Information We Collect**

**Personal Information**

In general, you can visit our Web site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you. Personal information like your name, address and e-mail address is obtained only when voluntarily submitted, such as when you register your software, subscribe to newsletters, respond to user surveys, register for programs or events or license software. Information that you supply will relate to the customer relationship that we have with you or your organization. 

**How We Use It**

If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet that we or our business partners request, it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information. 

We will use your personal information to fulfill subscription requests and orders for software and services made online and to provide other services you request. We may also use the information you supply to: 

  * Make the Web site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.
  * Help us customize content most relevant to you.
  * Notify you about important news concerning us, including new products and/or services, product updates and Customer Support issues, and special offers in which you may be interested.

In the process of administering our site, we maintain and track usage through Web server logs. Web server logs provide such information as what types of browsers are accessing our site, what pages receive high traffic, and the times of day our servers experience significant load. We use this information to improve the content and navigation features of our site. It is not used to personally identify you. 

**How We Share It**

We will not sell, rent or lease to others your personally identifiable information. We will share the personal data you provide only with other SAS entities and/or business partners who are acting on our behalf for the uses described above, except as provided below (see Consent). 

**Consent**

We will use and share the personally identifiable information you provided to us in ways related to those described above. We reserve the right to disclose any and all pertinent customer information to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. 

**Our Commitment to Data Security**

We are concerned about the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We use encryption technology when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information. 

**External Links**

Links to third-party Web sites from our Web site are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave our site. We do not control these sites and do not assume responsibility for any of these sites, their content, or their privacy policies. We do not endorse or make any representations about them or any information, software or other products or materials found there, or any results that may be obtained from using them. If you decide to access any of the third-party sites linked to our site, you do so at your own risk. 

**Cookies**

There are various technologies, including one called "cookies," which can be used to provide tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. Some of our pages use cookies or other technologies so that we can better serve you when you return to our site. We do not use cookies or similar technology to cross-relate personal information about our visitors. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. For more information, please refer to user information provided with your Web browser. 

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**

By using our Web site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Statement. If we change this Privacy Statement, the changes will be made on this page. Your continued use of our Web site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Statement will mean you accept those changes. 

**How to Contact Us**

Should you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Statement, please e-mail us at [privacy@sas.com.](mailto:privacy@sas.com)
